Guide to the A. Kenneth Pye, Chancellor, Records and Papers, 1960-1983 UA.06.51.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Chancellor of Duke University Records, 1976-1982
  - Subject Files, 1969-1983, bulk 1976-1982
    - Alumni: Organization, etc. 1976-1980 (Box 7)
    - Alumni Affairs: Alumni Meetings, 1980-1982 (Box 7)
    - Alumni Affairs: Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 7)
    - Alumni Affairs: Travel (Trish Roberts), 1979-1982 (Box 7)
    - Alumni Affairs: Paul Vick, Director, 1980-1982 (Box 7)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1976-1980 (Box 7)
    - ACE: American Council on Education, 1978-1980 (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - ACE: Commission of Collegiate Athletics, 1977 (2 folders (Box 7)
    - ACE: Commission on Collegiate Athletes, 1978-1980 (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - American Council on Education: Fellows Program, 1980-1982 (Box 8)
    - American Council on Education: Office of Governmental Regulations, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1980-1981 (Box 8)
    - American Dance Festival, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - American Musical Theatre, 1978-1980 (Box 8)
    - Angier B. Duke Scholarship Awards, 1976-81 (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Anthropology Department, 1978-1982 (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Applications (Wasiolek, S.; Ward, B.) 1978-1979 (Box 8)
    - Archives, Duke University, 1977-1979 (Box 8)
    - Art Department, 1976-1981 (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Art Museum, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Arts, Institute of the, 1980-1982 (Box 8)
    - Association of American Universities, 1979-1982 (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - DUAA.: Atlantic Coast Conference, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - DUAA: Basketball, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - DUAA: Budget, 1976-1980 (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - DUAA: Tom Butters, Athletic Director, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - DUAA: Club Sports, 1978-1982 (3 folders (Box 8)
    - DUAA: Football Association, 1980-1982 (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - DUAA: Football, 1975-1982 (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - DUAA: Department of Health, Physical Education, and Health, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - DUAA: Intercollegiate Athletics for Women, including Title IX, 1976-1981 (7 folders) (Box 9)
    - DUAA: Carl James, Director of Athletics, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
    - DUAA: Miscellaneous, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - DUAA: National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
    - DUAA: National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1979-1982 (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Auditing Program, 1978-1981 (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - B (Views on J. B. Rhine), 1980-1982 (Box 10)
    - Baldwin Auditorium, 1976-1978 (Box 10)
    - Benenson, Edward H. (Benenson Awards in Art History), 1976-1979 (Box 10)
    - Bevan, William (Provost), 1978-1982 (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Black Affairs, President's Council on, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Black Faculty Search, 1976-1982 (Box 10)
    - Black Studies: Black Affairs, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Blackburn, John O., 1975-1976 (Box 10)
    - Blaydon, Dr. Colin (Vice-Provost for Academic Policy and Planning), 1980-1982 (Box 10)
    - Botany Department, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Brown, Mr. and Mrs. W. Franklin, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Budget, 1976-1978 (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Budget, 1977-1981 (5 folders) (Box 11)
    - Budget Forecast, 1982-1983 (Box 11)
    - Budgets and Measurements Office: Harrison Brooke, Director, 1980-1982 (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Budgets and Measurements: Zero Based Budgeting, 1979-1983 (Box 11)
    - Bursar, 1980-1982 (Box 11)
    - Business and Finance: J. F. Adcock, Controller, 1976-1980 (Box 11)
    - Business and Finance: J. Peyton Fuller, 1976-1980 (Box 11)
    - Business and Finance: Charles B. Huestis, 1976-1980 (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - C, 1980-1982 (Box 11)
    - Cablevision, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Campus Services: J. G. Pietrantoni, Director, 1976-1981 (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Canadian Studies, 1976-1980 (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Carter Administration, 1976-1979 (Box 11)
    - Chairmen of Departments, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
    - Chancellor's Advisory Group, 1976-1978 (Box 11)
    - Chancellor's Letters: Directives to Faculty, Staff and Employees, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
    - Chapel: Benjamin N. Duke Memorial Organ, 1976-1978 (Box 11)
    - Chapel, 1978-1982 (3 folders) (Box 11)
    - Chapel: Campus Ministry (Hillel), 1978-1980 (Box 11)
    - Chapel: Campus Ministry, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Chapel: Robert T. Young, Minister to the University, 1976-1980 (Box 12)
    - Chemistry Department, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - China Exchange Program, 1980-1982 (Box 12)
    - Chronicle, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - Classical Studies Department, 1978-1982 (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Cleaveland, Frederick N., Provost, 1976-1979 (Box 12)
    - Cole, R. Taylor, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Commencement, 1977-1982 (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Commencement Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
    - Committee on Grants from Foreign Governments, 1973-1981 (Box 12)
    - Committee on the Allocation of Space in Union and Flowers Buildings, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - Committee on Squash-Racquet Ball Courts, 1982 (Box 12)
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1976-1980 (Box 12)
    - Commonwealth Studies Center, 1976-1980 (4 folders) (Box 12)
    - Community Relations, 1976-1978 (Box 12)
    - Computation Center, 1976-1980 (Box 12)
    - Computer Science Department, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Computing: Data Processing, General, 1977-1980 (Box 12)
    - Computing: Data Processing, Job Descriptions, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Computing: Mel Ray, Vice-Chancellor for Data Processing, 1978-1982 (4 folders) (Box 12)
    - Computing: Search Committee for Director of Computer Operations, 1976-1978 (Box 12)
    - Conflicts of Interest, 1977-1980 (Box 12)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1974-1978 (Box 13)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education: Clark Cahow Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education: Committee on Legislative and Public Policy, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education: General, 1978-1981 (Box 13)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education: Reports, 1978-1982 (3 folders) (Box 13)
    - Continuing Education, 1976-1982 (4 folders) (Box 13)
    - Counsel, University, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 13)
    - Counseling, Career, 1978-1980 (Box 13)
    - Counseling, Career: Faculty, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Counseling and Psychological Services (CAPS), 1976-1978 (Box 13)
    - Cultural Affairs, Office of, 1976-1978 (Box 13)
    - D, 1977-1982 (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Day Camp, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Deans, 1976-1980 (Box 13)
    - Deans' Council, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
    - Deans' Council: Probationary Period-Faculty Appointment, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Dean: Trinity College of Arts and Sciences (Ernestine Friedl), 1978-1980 (Box 13)
    - Dining Halls, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Directions for Progress, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Distinguished Professorships, 1978-1981 (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Divinity School: Deanship Search, 1976-1980 (Box 14)
    - Divinity School, 1980-1982 (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Duke Endowment: General Correspondence, 1976-1982 (4 folders) (Box 14)
    - Duke Endowment: Education Committee Meeting, 1982 Apr. 6 (Box 14)
    - Duke Endowment: Related Institutions - Meetings of Presidents, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Duke Endowment: Reports on Appropriations, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - Duke Endowment: Requests, 1976-1982 (5 folders) (Box 14)
    - Duke Endowment Suit, 1972-1977 (Box 14)
    - Durham Chamber of Commerce, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 14)
    - Durham, City of: Miscellaneous and Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 15)
    - Durham City Schools, 1976-1978 (Box 15)
    - Durham Health Care, 1976-1978 (Box 15)
    - E, 1979-1982 (Box 15)
    - E: Exxon Education Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 15)
    - East Campus Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
    - East Campus Activity Center: Memorial Gym Renovation Study, 1976-1978 (Box 15)
    - East Campus Proposal: Responses, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
    - Economics Department, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - Eads, Ralph: Texas Admissions Project, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
    - Education Department, 1976-1982 (4 folders) (Box 15)
    - Education Department: Committee to Study new Ed.D. Program in School Management, 1981-1982 (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - Education, Institute of, 1976-1978 (Box 15)
    - Education, U. S. Department of, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Educational Policy, Center for, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Ehle, John: Special Assistant to President Sanford for Cultural Affairs, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Emeriti, 1976-1981 (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Endowment: Statement of Endowment and Similar Funds by Fund, 1978-1981 (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Energy Committee: Energy Research, 1976-1978 (Box 15)
    - Energy Conservation, 1980-1982 (Box 15)
    - Energy Conservation: Water Conservation, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
    - Engineering School, 1976-1980 (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Engineering School, 1980-1982 (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - English Department, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Enrollments, 1978-1980 (Box 16)
    - Environmental Center, 1976-1980 (Box 16)
    - EEO: Affirmative Action - Handicapped, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - EEO: Affirmative Action Plan, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - EEO: Affirmative Action - Women, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - EEO: Lopez Study, 1982 (Box 16)
    - EEO: Miscellaneous and Correspondence, 1976-1982 (9 folders) (Box 16)
    - EEO: Policies and Regulations (HEW-University), 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - EEO: Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - EEO: Upward Mobility, 1978-1980 (Box 16)
    - EEO: Women's and Minorities, including Women's Network, 1976-1980 (Box 16)
    - EEO: Women's Network, 1980-1982 (Box 16)
    - Erasmus Club, 1978-1980 (Box 16)
    - Executive Health Program, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - Expressway, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - F, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Faculty Club, 1976-1981 (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Faculty: Departmental Review, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - Faculty Evaluations, 1976-1978 (Box 16)
    - Faculty Handbook (Benefits), 1978-1980 (Box 16)
    - Faculty: Miscellaneous, 1976-1980 (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Faculty: Promotion and Tenure, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Faculty Scholarship Fund, 1976-1978 (Box 17)
    - Federal Relations: AAU (Association of American Universities), Council on AAU Relations, 1976-1978 (Box 17)
    - Federal Relations: Ad Hoc Group, 1976-1981 (4 folders) (Box 17)
    - Federal Relations: Committee on, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Federal Relations: Lucy Knight, Coordinator, 1978-1982 (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Federal Relations: General, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 17)
    - Federal Relations: Robert S. Havely, Director of Government Relations, 1982 (Box 17)
    - Federal Relations: OMB Circular A21, 1978-1980 (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Federal Relations: Tax, 1976-1981 (4 folders) (Box 17)
    - Federal Relations: Tuition Tax Credits, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Financial Aid: Awards, Applications, Reports and Federal Agencies, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Financial Aid: Dr. Cahow, 1980-1982 (Box 17)
    - Financial Aid: Distribution of Funds; Projected Needs, 1976-1978 (Box 17)
    - Financial Aid: Federal Program, 1981-1982 (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Financial Aid: Federally Insured Loan Funds, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Financial Aid: Miscellaneous, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Financial Aid: NDSL Funds, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Financial Aid Planning: Dr. Cahow, 1978-1980 (Box 18)
    - Financial Aid Planning, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
    - Financial Aid: Planning Report, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Financial Aid: Scholarship Funds, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Financial Aid: State Aid to Private Universities, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Financial Aid: Student Loan Office, 1976-1981 (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Financial Aid: Work Study Funds, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Fletcher, A. J., 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Florida National Bank, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Forest, Duke, 1979-1982 (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Forestry, School of, 1976-1982 (4 folders) (Box 18)
    - Foundation, Mary Duke Biddle, 1978-1980 (Box 18)
    - Foundation, Max Fleischmann, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Foundation, Ford, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Founders' Day, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
    - Fozzard, Peter, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
    - Friedl, Dr. Ernestine: Dean, Trinity College, 1980-1982 (Box 18)
    - Friends Proposal, 1978 (Box 18)
    - Fringe Benefits, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Fringe Benefits: Tuition Remission, 1976-1980 (Box 18)
    - Fringe Benefits: Tuition Remission (Children of Methodist Ministers), 1980-1982 (Box 18)
    - Fulbright and Jaworski (Cary W. Vogt), 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Fuller, J. Peyton: Corporate Controller, 1980-1982 (Box 18)
    - Fuqua School of Business, 1981-1982 (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Fuqua School of Business: Building Program, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
    - G, 1980-1982 (Box 19)
    - G (Duke Gardens), 1976-1978 (Box 19)
    - Geller, George B., 1978-1981 (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Geology Department, 1978-1980 (Box 19)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature Department, 1978-1982 (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Government Regulation of Business, Professorship in, 1976-1978 (Box 19)
    - Grading Studies (Undergraduate), 1976 (Box 19)
    - Grads, 1980-1982 (Box 19)
    - Graduate School: Craufurd D. W. Goodwin, Dean, 1980-1982 (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Graduate School: John C. McKinney, 1976-1978 (Box 19)
    - Graduate School: Miscellaneous, 1976-1980 (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1974-1979 (5 folders) (Box 19)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration: Building Plans, 1977-1980 (Box 19)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration: Management Sciences Degree, 1977-1978 (Box 19)
    - Green, William L. (Director of Public Information), 1976-1978 (Box 19)
    - H, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 20)
    - Hagel, Miss Gail, 1977-1979 (Box 20)
    - Hamner, W. Clay: Hotel Project, 1980-1982 (Box 20)
    - Harward, Stephen C., 1977-1979 (Box 20)
    - Hazardous Waste Regulations, 1979-1981 (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - HEW Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1975-1980 (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Health Policy, Center for, 1980-1981 (Box 20)
    - Henderson, R. James, Business Manager, 1980-1982 (Box 20)
    - Hillman, Jennifer, Research Assistant to Chancellor, 1979-1981 (Box 20)
    - History Department, 1976-1980 (Box 20)
    - Homesites, 1976-1980 (Box 20)
    - Honor Code, 1979 (Box 20)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1980 (Box 20)
    - Hotel-Conference Center, 1979-1980 (Box 20)
    - Housing: Central Campus, 1978 (Box 20)
    - Housing: Dormitories, Fraternities, etc., 1976-1980 (Box 20)
    - Housing: General, 1979-1980 (Box 20)
    - Human Resources, Department of: State of North Carolina, 1978 (Box 20)
    - Humanities, National Endowment for the, 1978-1980 (Box 20)
    - Humanities Council, 1975-1977 (Box 20)
    - I, 1981-1982 (Box 20)
    - I: Interdisciplinary Course and Faculty Seminar, 1979-1980 (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Annual Giving Reports, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Campaign Steering Committee, 1977 (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Capital Gifts Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement, Trustee Committee on, 1977-1980 (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Development Officers, 1976-1981 (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Development Summary to President, 1978-1980 (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Gift Prospects, 1969-1978 (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Gift Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Gift Records Office, 1974-1980 (Box 20)
    - Institutional Advancement: Gifts Records Office, 1974-1982 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Richard Hayes, 1977-1978 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement, 1977-1981 (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Individual, Corporate and Foundation Proposals Pending, 1977-1982 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Internal Development Committee, 1977-1980 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Loyalty Found, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Gerald McBride, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Ralph McCaughan, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: John McNabb, 1977-1979 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: John McNabb (Transition Paper), 1979 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Andy Parker Assistant Director of Development, 1978-1983 (3 folders) (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Marion Peavey, 1977-1881 (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Policy Statements (Handling of Gifts, Endowed Professorships, etc.) 1973-1975 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Post-Epoch Planning, 1977-1978 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: President's Associates, 1977-1980 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Private Gifts, Grants, Contracts (Reports), 1980-1981 (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: Paul Robell, 1976-1978 (Box 21)
    - Institutional Advancement: J. David Ross, 1977-1979 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Institutional Advancement: Scholarship Budget, 1980-1982 (Box 22)
    - Institutional Advancement: Barbara Smith, Foundation Relations Officer, 1978-1982 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Institutional Advancement, Trustee Committee for, 1980-1982 (Box 22)
    - Institutional Advancement: University Budget Committee, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Insurance, 1978-1982 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Interdisciplinary Courses, 1979-1980 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Internal Audit Office, 1976-1980 (Box 22)
    - International Security and Disarmament (Duke-UNC Report to Ford Foundation), 1977-1979 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - International Security and Disarmament, 1980-1982 (Box 22)
    - Investments, 1979-1981 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - J, 1978-1982 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Jantz Collection, 1977-1980 (Box 22)
    - Judaic Studies, 1981-1982 (Box 22)
    - K, 1979-1982 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Kreps, Juanita (Secretary of Commerce), 1980 (Box 22)
    - Kreps, Juanita, 1981-1982 (Box 22)
    - L, 1977-1980 (Box 22)
    - Labor Relations, 1977-1982 (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Law School, 1977-1982 (Box 22)
    - Lewis, Harold W., Vice-Provost, 1976-1980 (Box 22)
    - Library: Connie Dunlap, 1976-1980 (Box 22)
    - Library: Miscellaneous, 1976-1982 (5 folders) (Box 23)
    - Living History Program, 1980-1982 (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Luce Foundation, 1972-1978 (Box 23)
    - M, 1976-1980 (Box 23)
    - Marine Laboratory, 1976-1982 (4 folders) (Box 23)
    - Marine Laboratory: Duke-UNC Oceanographic Consortium, 1977-1981 (Box 23)
    - Marshal, University, 1976-1980 (Box 23)
    - Marshall, Roger L. (Rufus Powell), 1981-1982 (Box 23)
    - Mathematics Department, 1978-1982 (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Medieval and Renaissance Studies (Southern Institute of Medieval and Renaissance Studies), 1976-1980 (Box 23)
    - Mellon, Andrew Foundation, 1978-1981 (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Methodists: Board of Higher Education and Ministry Universities, 1978-1980 (Box 23)
    - Methodist Minister: Tuition Remission Program, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Minority Affairs, Office of, 1978-1979 (Box 23)
    - Microelectronics Center of North Carolina (MCNC), 1980-1981 (5 folders) (Box 23)
    - MCNC, 1982 (Box 24)
    - MCNC Board Meeting, 1980 July (Box 24)
    - MCNC Board Meeting, 1980 Oct. (Box 24)
    - MCNC Board Meeting, 1981 Jan. (Box 24)
    - MCNC Board Meeting, 1981 Apr. (Box 24)
    - MCNC Board Meeting, 1981 July (Box 24)
    - MCNC Board Meeting, 1981 Oct. (Box 24)
    - MCNC Board Meeting, 1982 Jan. (Box 24)
    - MCNC Board Meeting, 1982 Apr. (Box 24)
    - MCNC Special Meeting, 1981 June (Box 24)
    - Music Department (Mary Lou Williams), 1976-1980 (Box 24)
    - Music Department, 1980-1982 (Box 24)
    - Music Department (Ethel Sieck Carrabina), 1981-1982 (Box 24)
    - N, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1976-1981 (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1980-1982 (Box 24)
    - National Humanities Center, 1977-1982 (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - National Science Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 24)
    - Nixon, Richard M. Library, 1981-1982 (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - Nixon Library (Letters, Editorials), 1981-1982 (Box 24)
    - Non-academic Employees: Opportunities for Advancement, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
    - North Carolina Central University, 1978-1981 (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - North Carolina School of Science and Math, 1980-1982 (Box 25)
    - North Carolina, University of, 1977-1981 (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Notre Dame: Conference on Legal Problems of Independent Higher Education, 1978 Oct. (Box 25)
    - O, 1978-1979 (Box 25)
    - Oral History Program, 1978-1982 (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Overhead Rates, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
    - P, 1980-1982 (Box 25)
    - P (Psychical Research Center), 1978-1980 (Box 25)
    - Patents, 1972-1977 (Box 25)
    - Patent Office, 1974-1982 (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Payroll Office, 1978 (Box 25)
    - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Company, 1981 (Box 25)
    - Personnel Department, 1978-1980 (Box 25)
    - Personnel, 1980-1982 (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Personnel: Employment Policies, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
    - Personnel: Richard L. Jackson, Director, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
    - Personnel: Job Planning and Achievement Review), 1976 (Box 25)
    - Personnel: W. H. Johnston, Director of Human Resources, 1982-1983 (Box 25)
    - Personnel: Miscellaneous (Layoffs), 1976-1978 (Box 25)
    - Personnel: Personnel Policies, 1977 (Box 25)
    - Phi Beta Zeta: Revocation of Charter, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Philosophy Department, 1977-1981 (Box 25)
    - Physical Plant Department, 1979-1982 (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Physics Department, 1977-1982 (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Placement Office, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
    - Policies, University, 1971-1980 (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Policy Sciences, Institute of, 1976-1981 (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Policy Sciences, Institute of, 1980-1981 (Box 26)
    - Policy Sciences, Institute of: Joel Fleishman, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 26)
    - Political Science Department, 1979-1982 (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Political Science Department (T. Lomperis Correspondence), 1976-1978 (Box 26)
    - Powe, Porter, Alphin and Whichard, 1981 (Box 26)
    - Powell, Rufus, 1978-1980 (Box 26)
    - Pre-School Laboratory, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - President's House, 1981 (Box 26)
    - Press, Duke, 1978-1982 (3 folders) (Box 26)
    - Press, Duke, Task Force on, 1978 (Box 26)
    - Primate Facility, 1978-1979 (Box 26)
    - Primate Center, 1980-1982 (Box 26)
    - Privacy Policy: Students, 1977 (Box 26)
    - Provost Search Committee, 1978 (Box 26)
    - Psychological Services Center, 1979-1980 (Box 26)
    - Psychology Department, 1976-1982 (3 folders) (Box 26)
    - Publications Division, 1977-1979 (Box 27)
    - Q - R, 1979-1982 (Box 27)
    - Questionnaires: Academic Departments, 1976 (Box 27)
    - R, 1976-1980 (Box 27)
    - Reagan Administration, 1981-1982 (Box 27)
    - Recombinant DNA Research, 1977-1980 (Box 27)
    - Reference, Letters of (Larry Ladd), 1976-1980 (Box 27)
    - Reference, Letters of, 1980-1982 (Box 27)
    - Registrar, 1976-1982 (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Religion Department, 1976-1980 (Box 27)
    - Religion Department (Nomination of C. Eric Lincoln for J. B. Duke Professorship), 1980-1982 (Box 27)
    - Religious Activities (Campus Ministry), 1976-1977 (Box 27)